Rage. Riot. Rebirth.
10,000 Saints is a comedy, drama, music film directed by Shari Springer Berman.
A sweeping multigenerational story set against the backdrop of the raw, roaring New York City of the late 1980s; adoption, teen pregnancy, drugs, hardcore punk rock, the unbridled optimism and reckless
stupidity of the young—and old—are all major elements in this heart-aching tale of the son of diehard hippies and his strange odyssey through the extremes of late 20th century youth culture.
Les Horn, played by Ethan Hawke.
Jude Keffy-Horn, played by Asa Butterfield.
Diane Urbanski, played by Emily Mortimer.
Harriet, played by Julianne Nicholson.
Eliza Urbanski, played by Hailee Steinfeld.
Johnny, played by Emile Hirsch.
Ten Thousand Saints is a 2015 American drama film written and
directed by Shari Springer Berman and Robert Pulcini.
It is based on the novel of the same name by Eleanor Henderson.
The film stars Asa Butterfield as Jude Keffy-Horn, the protagonist of the story.
The film premiered at the 2015 Sundance Film Festival on January 23, 2015.
The film was released in a limited release and through video on
demand on August 14, 2015 by Screen Media Films.
The film explores themes of new york city, woman director, indifferent.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.